const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'According to legend, who was the first person to discover the coffee plant?',
        answers: [
            'Kaldi, a Goat Herder',
            'Christopher Columbus',
            'Simba, King of Ethiopia',
            'Julius Caesar',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Kaldi, a Goat Herder',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Government required men to provide coffee for their wives or be threatened with divorce?',
        answers: [
            '1st Century Roman Empire',
            '16th Century Ottoman Turkish Empire',
            '17th Century Colonial British Empire',
            '20th Century Soviet Union',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '16th Century Ottoman Turkish Empire',
    },
    {
        question: 'When was the first Espresso Machine invented?',
        answers: [
            '1912',
            '1933',
            '1942',
            '1970',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1933',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which coffee bean is considered to be superior in quality and flavor?',
        answers: [
            'Arabica',
            'Cafe',
            'Espresso',
            'Robusta',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Arabica',
    },
    {
        question: 'Latin American Coffees are processed primarily by which method?',
        answers: [
            'Natural Processing',
            'Semi-Washed Processing',
            'Simple Processing',
            'Washed Processing',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Washed Processing',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is one unique benefit to the natural processing the coffee bean?',
        answers: [
            'It keeps the fruit intact while obtaining the coffee bean.',
            'The coffee bean often has a more  fruity and juicy flavor.',
            'It increases the caffeine content greatly.',
            'It has no significant difference than other processing methods which use water.',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The coffee bean often has a more  fruity and juicy flavor.',
    },
    {
        question: 'How many times will a coffee tree produce coffee cherries?',
        answers: [
            'Once a decade',
            'Once a year',
            'Once a month',
            'Once a week',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Once a year',
    },
    {
        question: 'How many years can a coffee tree stay productive with proper care?',
        answers: [
            '1-5 years',
            '5-10 years',
            '20-25 years',
            '40 years',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '20-25 years'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which geographical region is known for its full bodied and “spicy” coffee flavors?',
        answers: [
            'Africa/Arabia',
            'Asia/Pacific',
            'Europe',
            'Latin America',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Asia/Pacific',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the ideal elevation to grow quality coffee trees?',
        answers: [
            '0-400 meters',
            '500-800 meters',
            '900-1,800 meters',
            'Elevation has no effect on coffee bean quality.',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '900-1,800 meters',
    }
];